Khayan Malantrucco

Agile Coach | Kanban Management Professional (KMP)

Dedicated and passionate Agile Leader with 7+ years in different business, experienced in Agile methodology implementation and optimization. Aspire to share my expertise to help organizations meet their goals efficiently.

EXPERIENCE

Mooven, São Paulo — Agile Coach

March 2022 - Current

Championed the adoption of Agile practices in multiple organizations and business (technology, fashion, agribusiness, banking, credit, retail, among others), facilitating learning and development and promoting a proactive approach to change management; Led the Agile transformation, increasing the team's productivity and predictability through the Kanban Maturity Model and other continuous improvement best practices.

ModalGR, Santos — Scrum Master | Agile Leader

May 2021 - March 2022

Promote a collaborative and high-performance environment, encouraging open communication between team members, as well as Agile culture, ensuring that principles and best practices are applied at the Organization's different service levels. Guide and train employees on the use of the Scrum framework, making more efficient and effective deliveries. Organize and facilitate Scrum ceremonies. Work on solving problems and seeking improvements in the Organization's processes.

Magma3, Santos — Software Developer | Product Owner

July 2020 - May 2021

Design, develop and maintain applications using the .NET Framework and JavaScript. Implement solutions and cloud services using AWS solutions. Analyze business needs and processes, mapping points for improvement, promoting solutions that meet the organization's objectives.

ModalGR, Santos — Full Stack Developer | Scrum Master

May 2019 - April 2020

Enable the team to use Scrum good practices for managing software development work and monitoring flow efficiency metrics. Collaborate with customers and stakeholders to understand their needs and translate requirements into clear technical specifications. Development of web software using ASP.NET Core and ReactJS.

Santos, SP, Brazil khayan.malantrucco@gmail.com in/khayanmalantrucco +55 13 98181-3437

SKILLS

- Agile Methodologies
- Problem-Solving
- Change Management
- Strategic Thinking
- Communication
- Leadership
- Mentorship
- Facilitation
- Coaching

CERTIFICATION

- KMP Kanban
 Management Professional
- KSI Kanban Systems Improvement
- KSD Kanban System Design
- Flow Metrics Practitioner

LANGUAGES

- Portuguese Native
- English C1 Advanced
- Spanish B1 Average

FATEC Rubens Lara, Santos — Scrum Master | Team Leader

January 2018 – December 2018

Planning, prioritization and development of FATEC Santos digital marketing and social media demands. Management of the delivery schedule, facilitation between the development team and project progression. Creation of content, monitoring of publications and team performance indicators.

EDUCATION

Master of Strategic Business Process Management

PUC Minas, Belo Horizonte | April 2020 - November 2022

Associate of Technology: Internet Systems Degree

FATEC Rubens Lara, Santos | January 2017 - December 2019